http://www.kiewit.com/info/privacy-statement/

HomeMarketsAbout UsProjectsServicesNewsroomCareersLocationsCOVID-19
Search
HomeMarketsBuildingIndustrialMiningOil, Gas & ChemicalPowerTransportationWater/WastewaterAbout UsOur Core ValuesHistoryAwardsComplianceCompany StoreProjectsBuildingIndustrialMiningOil, Gas & ChemicalPowerTransportationWater/WastewaterServicesEngineeringProcurementFoundationsDevelopmentNewsroomCareersLocationsCOVID-19
WEBSITE Privacy Statement
Home
Info
Website Privacy Statement
Info
SitemapWebsite Privacy StatementTerms & ConditionsContact UsAccessibility
Kiewit Careers
From surveyors to heavy equipment mechanics, field engineers to hazard analysts, we provide an incredible range of opportunities.
Apply Today
Kieways Magazine
The all new Kieways Magazine
Read More
WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT
Kiewit Corporation, and its affiliates and subsidiaries (the "Company"), own and operate a number of Internet domains, including but not limited to this Website (the "Website"). This statement describes the Company's Website privacy practices.
WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?
You may be asked at various times to provide data such as your name, e-mail address and phone number (the "Personally Identifiable Information"), as well as information about what you like or do not like about the Website. The Company collects Personally Identifiable Information online primarily to make it easier for you to use the Website, to allow us to improve our website and our services, and for us to communicate with you.
Our data collection policies are intended to allow you to choose how much Personally Identifiable Information to provide to us. Information collected online is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable:
Anonymous Information refers to information that cannot easily be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, we may know that 10,000 people visit this Privacy Statement page today, but we do not necessarily know their names, where they live, or their date of birth.
Personally Identifiable Information tells us who you are. We may need this information to provide personalized or enhanced service that you request. While we hope that you will find it beneficial to judiciously provide Personally Identifiable Information so that we can provide the best practical service to you, the amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose is a decision you make.
When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser automatically transmits some information to The Company every time you access our Website. Examples of such information include the URL of the Web page you were just on (known as the "Refer"), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, and the browser version you are using to access our site. Some of this information may be collected by the Company to help us improve our Website and our services. For instance, we may use this information to ensure the content you request is presented in the best format.
To activate some of the features available within the Website, we may assign "cookies" to your Internet browser. On our system, a cookie is a small text file that contains a unique identification number stored on your computer. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser to our server computers when you interact with our Website. When you agree to provide Personally Identifiable Information directly to us, we may assign cookies that identify you, personally, to our servers.
WHAT ORGANIZATION IS COLLECTING THE INFORMATION?
The data you provide is collected by the Company. Some areas of our Website read data that creates, or has created, an Anonymous Profile. Other areas require you to register or login before you can access an area of the Website. These areas read and store Personally Identifiable Information that specifically identifies you to our servers.
HOW WILL THE ANONYMOUS PROFILE INFORMATION BE USED?
Below is a description of some of the uses of the information that we collect and how our users benefit from these actions:
We try to pay attention to what our users use and do not use on our Website, and we modify our content appropriately. Many of the pages in our Website collect Anonymous Profile Information. The creation of an anonymous profile allows the Company to identify the information that users find most useful. We may use these anonymous profiles to improve our Website's content and format, and our company's services. This is essential to our ability to provide high quality content to you.
HOW WILL THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION BE USED?
Our Website may require that you provide Personally Identifiable Information to use a Website feature. We may use this information for internal research regarding the use of our Website and to facilitate the feature you choose to use.
To the extent possible, we indicate the informational fields that are required to use a feature we offer. You have the option of not providing this information to us by choosing to not use the related feature of our Website.
If you correspond with us through letters or email messages, we may store such correspondence with whatever other information you have provided to us. By submitting such correspondence, you agree that we may use your information and contact you in response.
In addition to the uses described in this section, the Company will use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us and information we collect about your use of our Website to improve access to our Website, improve the content and organization of our Website, resolve disputes, and correct technical problems with the Website.
WHAT INFORMATION WILL WE DISTRIBUTE?
The Company retains Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us, only for our use and that of our affiliated companies. We do not sell your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties. But although we use industry standard hardware and software designed to protect your privacy, we cannot guarantee and you should not expect that the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us will always remain confidential
If a feature of our Website requires that you register with our Website, you will be required to choose a user name and a password You are responsible for protecting the confidentiality of both. Should you allow another to access our Website through your user name and password, the Company will assume that you are accessing our Website and you will be responsible for all actions taken in your name. By using our Website, you accept responsibility for all activity undertaken in your name.
If you register with us, you will have the option of accessing and changing your password. You may also change certain other information you provided to us. If you have any questions, send an email message to webmaster@kiewit.com. Our server computers may retain whatever Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, and such data could potentially be made available for distribution to third parties as required by law, such as to law-enforcement agencies or pursuant to subpoenas or other court orders. The Company may also share both Anonymous Profile Information and Personally Identifiable Information to investigate allegations of fraud or other unlawful activities, civil offenses, and violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use. In such case, the Company shall have no obligation to notify you of, or to decline, any appropriately documented request for Personally Identifiable Information or Anonymous Profile Information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Company Websites. The Company does not control the information collection and distribution policies on Internet domains other than on the Company Internet domains. As a service to our users, the Company Website may provide links to other sites. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage all users to read the privacy statements of each and every Website.
WHAT CHOICES ARE AVAILABLE REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF THE INFORMATION?
We encourage you to share information only with those websites that provide true value to you in exchange for your information and that commit to privacy practices that are acceptable to you. We believe that the Company's websites provide such value, but it is ultimately your choice to share Personally Identifiable Information with the Company.
While the Company does not sell any Personally Identifiable Information you submit to our Website to any other parties, the Company reserves the right to use such information for any lawful purpose, including but not limited to recruiting, marketing, performance monitoring and statistical analysis.
The Company reserves the right to update this statement. When we do, we will place a notice on our Website. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy statement periodically and become aware of modifications. By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this privacy statement. If you do not agree, you are not permitted to use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
The Company also reserves the right to send registration confirmations, Service Alerts and similar messages to our users to inform them of specific changes that may impact their ability to use our Website, regardless of such users' e-mail contact opt-in status. The Company retains these rights because we may need the right to contact you as a matter of law or regarding matters that may be important to you.
Questions regarding this Privacy Statement may be submitted to the Company’s Privacy Officer via e-mail at privacy@kiewit.com, or by phone at: 1 (833) 950-1724.
Version - Feb 2020
Quick Links
Home
Markets
About Us
Projects
Our Commitment
Media
Long Beach, Cal.
Read More
TD Ameritrade Headquarters
Omaha, Neb.
Long Beach, Cal.
Read More
TD Ameritrade Headquarters
Omaha, Neb.
Read More
Contact Kiewit
Home Office :
3555 Farnam St. Omaha, NE
Locations Page   |   Career Search
© 2020 Kiewit Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
